

# MINH TAI NGUY

Software Engineering

Gitlab: https://gitlab.com/tainguy2211



Email: tai.nguy22112000@gmail.com

🔪 Phone: +(84) 0909234204

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/tai-nguy-m2211



Address: District 10, Ho Chi Minh City

### Summary

I am a fresh mechatronics engineer at Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology. I have almost 2years of expriences in Bach Khoa Research Center for Manufactoring Engineering. I am looking for an opportunity to grow my career in the software development field, to build great products that scale and drive positive impacts on many users. Therefore, I am willing to face several challenges to take benefits and bring various values as well as my claim company.



#### **Education**

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology – Vietnam National University

Aug 2018 - Present

## Mechatronics Engineering

Cumulative GPA: 8,06/10

#### Achievements:

- International article at International Journal of Systems Signal Control and **Engineering Application**
- Creativity Award at Humanoid Robot Competition
- Graduation Thesis: Medicine and Medical Equipments Management System in Hospital

## 

#### **Work Experience**

National Key Lab for Digital Control and System Engineering

June 2020 - April 2021

#### Researcher

Research Project: - Study on the control algorithm for Autonomous Underwater Helicopter My responsibilities:

- Research, design and simulate the 3D models for AUH.

Bach Khoa Research Center for Manufacturing Engineering – BK RECME

April 2021 – April 2022

#### Leader

Research Project: - Website for Medicine and Medical Equipments Management System https://smartbag-web.herokuapp.com/

> - Website for Bach Khoa Research Center for Manufacturing Engineering https://bkrecme-web.herokuapp.com/

## My responsibilities:

- Design Front-end and Web Server for Medicine and Medical Equipments Management System
- Design Front-end for BK-RECME's Website.



#### Skills

Language English

**Programming Language** Python, JavaScripts, C/C++

Front-end React, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, MUI Library, Figma

Back-end NodeJS, Strapi

**Dev Tools** Gitlab, Github, VSCode

**Database** MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebase Realtime Database